Guide to the E. Ethelbert Miller papers, 1936-2021, bulk 1962-2018 MS2215
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Ethelbert Miller materials, 1962-2018; 1940-2021; Series 1; Miller, E. Ethelbert
  - All material donated before 2008, Series 1 Subseries 1; 24 linear feet
    - Programs, posters, flyers (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Programs, newsletters (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Programs, flyers (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Programs, flyers, features (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Programs, flyers, posters (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Programs, flyers, posters (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Programs, flyers (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Programs, flyers (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Programs, flyers, posters (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Programs, flyers, posters (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Programs, flyers (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Programs, flyers (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Programs, posters, flyers (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Programs, posters, flyers (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Programs, posters (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Programs, flyers, brochures (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Programs, posters, flyers (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Programs, newsletters (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Programs, clippings (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Programs, clippings (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Programs, clippings, invitations (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Programs, clippings, invitations (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Magazines, clippings (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Flyers, brochures, booklets (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Announcements (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Daily Planner, 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Daily Planner, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Daily Planner, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Daily Planner, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Daily Planner, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Daily Planner, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Daily Planner, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Daily Planner, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Daily Planner, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Daily Planner, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Daily Planner, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Daily Planner, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Daily Planner, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Daily Planner, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Daily Planner, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Daily Planner, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Daily Planner, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Daily Planner, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Calendar, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Address and telephone book (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Address and telephone book (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Address and telephone book (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Address book (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Appointment book (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Personal diary (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Personal diary (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Personal diary (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Personal diary (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Personal notes (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Daily planner, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Daily planner, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Scrapbook: Clippings, programs, flyers (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Scrapbook: clippings (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Scrapbook: clippings, flyers (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Scrapbook: clippings, flyers (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Scrapbook: clippings, flyers (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Scrapbook: clippings, flyers (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Scrapbook: flyers, clippings (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Scrapbook: flyers, posters, clippings (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Scrapbook: Clippings, flyers (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Certificates (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Certificates (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Ceremonies (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Achievements, thanks, awards (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Recognitions, acknowledgements, 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Proposals (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Invitations (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Awards (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Award - Pen Oakland (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Awards (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Photographs (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Photographs (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Photographs (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Photographs (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Photographs (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Photographs (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Photographs, negatives (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Photographs (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Photographs (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Photographs (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Photographs (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Correspondence: A (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: B (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: C (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: D (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: E, F (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: G (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: H, I, J (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: K, L (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: M (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence: M continued (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence: M continued (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence: N (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence: P, Q (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence: R (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence: S (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence: T, U, V (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence: W (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence: X, Y, Z (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence: A (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence: B, C, D (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence: E, F, G (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence: H, I, J (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence: J, K (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence: M (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence: N, O, P, Q (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence: R, S (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence: T, U, V (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence: T, U, V continued (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence: W (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence: X, Y, Z (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence: postcards (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence: postcards (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence: The Zen Book (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence: June Jordan (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Correspondence (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Correspondence (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Correspondence (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Correspondence (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Correspondence (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Correspondence: Fathering Words responses (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: Fathering Words responses (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: Black Science Fiction writers (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: National Endowment for the Humanities (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: Omar Bagadas (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: condolences, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: condolences, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: condolences, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: condolences, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1984-2004 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1984-2004 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence: Transition magazine (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence: from Ethelbert Miller (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence: to Ethelbert Miller (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence: postcards (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Correspondence: Jenny Bent (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Correspondence: letters from St. Martin press (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Correspondence: letters of thanks (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Correspondence (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Binder: How We Sleep on the Nights We Don't Make Love (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Binder: How We Sleep on the Nights We Don't Make Love (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Binder: Wild Washington Animal Sculptures A - Z (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Binder: mixed materials (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Binder: Deser Nights Rising Star writers conference, 03/2003 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Binder: Correspondence (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Binder: Readings, talks, publications, contracts (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Binder: Fathering Words (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Binder: Fathering Words, mixed material (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Class record book (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Class record book (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - A Directory of Washington's African American Poets, 01/1979 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Howard University H book, 1977-1979 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Howard University Accession Directory, 1976-1977 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Howard University Department of Afro-American Studies booklet, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Humanities profiles (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Hardy Middle school materials (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - PLA National Conference materials, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Institute for policy studies materials (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Institute for policy studies materials (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Black men research (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Black men research (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Multicultural Review materials (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - D.C. Jewish Community Center (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - D.C. Jewish Community center (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - N.W.U. (National Writers Union) (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - AWP Pedagogy forum, 04/1994 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - AWP materials (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - AWP materials (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Artist Hiro materials (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - AWP(Associated Writers Programs) materials (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - AWP conference materials (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Southern Festival of Books (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Workshops materials (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - National Writers Union materials (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Report: The Institute for the Arts and Humanities, 07/15/1975 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Audio tapes: Chasen Gaver (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Audio Tapes: Chasen Gaver (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Audio Tapes: Chasen Gaver (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - National Multi Cultural Institute (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Washington Independent Writers: minutes, correspondence (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - National Independent Writers: minutes, correspondence (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Festival of Poets and Poetry of St. Marys, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Blues Aesthetic Advisory committee (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Floppy disks (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Pen/Faulkner Award materials, 1995-1996 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Leadership Washington (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - American University (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Howard University Hotel project (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - HBCU (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - New York City meeting, 09/16/1996 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Folger (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - The National Council on the Aging (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Alexandria public schools poetry book (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Energy Blacksouth press, financial data (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - D.C. Arts Commision (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Energy Blacksouth press: flyers and articles (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Jasmine Miller materials (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Jasmine Miller materials (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Name tags (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Name tags (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Early education materials (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Family materials (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Richard Egberto Miller funeral service, 12/15/1985 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Egberto M. Miller funeral services, 02/06/1987 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Assignment: the personal and the political, 04/18/1986 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Phillip Jerry Poetry contest winners, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Black Issues in Higher Education, 1995-1998 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Black Issues in Higher Education: information packets (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous materials (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous materials (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous materials (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous materials (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous materials (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous materials, 1997-2000 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous materials (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous materials (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous materials (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous materials (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous materials (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Miscellaneous materials (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous materials (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Miscellaneous materials (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous materials (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous materials (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Miscellaneous materials (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Miscellaneous materials (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Miscellaneous materials (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Miscellaneous materials (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Miscellaneous materials (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Miscellaneous materials (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Oversized posters, flyers (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Oversized posters, flyers, programs (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Pins, buttons (Box 17, Folder 1)
      General note
      various pins and buttons
  - Poet files, 1969-2009; 1969-2020; Series 1 Subseries 2
    This subseries is arranged alphabetically.
    This subseries contains correspondence, promotional materials and works by various poets amassed by Ethelbert Miller. These files are organized alphabetically by author. Materials range in date from 1969-2020, with the bulk of the material dating from 1969-2009. Providing not only a comprehensive list of nearly all the prominent poets and writers to emerge from the Washington D.C. area, these files also demonstrate the far reach of Ethelbert Miller's influence on those around him. Please note that correspondence within this subseries may overlap with files within subseries 1.
    Poetry -- Workshops; Poetry -- African American poets; Correspondence; Public speaking; Performance poetry; Alvarez, Julia; Walker, Alice; Gilmore, Brian
    - Abraham, Eric John: correspondence [1 of 2], 1986-1989 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Abrahamson, Eric John: correspondence [2 of 2], 1984-1994 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Abubakar, Tanimu, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Achebe, Chinua, 1988-1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Achtenberg, Anya: correspondence, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Adams, Lea, 1991; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Adisa, Opal, 1997; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Adkins, Keith, 1994-1997; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Ado, Gustave Firmin, 1998-1999; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Adwan, Mamdooh S., Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Afer-Anderson, Terrance, 1997; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Afif, Fatima, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - Ai: promotional matrial, articles, 1973-2004 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Ai: correspondence, clippings, 1976-1980 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - African American Writers Guild, 1987-1988 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - A Gathering of the Tribes, 2003; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 191, Folder 5)
    - Anglesey, Zoe: articles, promotinal material, 1988-1994 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Anglesey, Zoe: works by, 1991-2002 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Anglesey, Zoe: correspondence [1 of 2], 1982-1992 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Anglesey, Zoe: correspondence [2 of 2], 1993-2003 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Ajayi, Jare, 1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - Alam, Juan S., 1980-1984; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - Alenier, Karren, 1984-1992, 2000; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - Alexander, Elizabeth: postcards, cards, 1986-1996 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Alexander, Elizabeth: correspondence, 1986-1990 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Alexander, Elizabeth: clippings, reviews, 1990-1994 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Ali, Abdul, 2007-2008; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 71, Folder 13)
    - Ali, Agha Shahid: correspondence, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Ali, Jamal, 1984-1989; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 71, Folder 14)
    - Allah, Fareedah, 1981, 1983; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 71, Folder 15)
    - Allen-Yazzie, Chrstine, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 71, Folder 16 (1/2))
    - Allen-Yazzie, Christine, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 71, Folder 17 (2/2))
    - Allen, Christine: correspondence, works by, 1996-1997 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Allen, Jeffery Renard: correspondence, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Allen, Jeffery Renard: works by, undated (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Allen, Samuel: flyer, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Alleyne, Mark, 1985-1988; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 72)
    - Almandi, Zaehraa'a, 1976; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Alperovitz, Gar, 1991-1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Alvarez, Julia: correspondence, 1985-1993 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Alvarez, Julia: profiles, 1986-1996 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Alvarez, Julia: reviews, 1990-1991 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Alvarez, Julia: flyers, undated (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Alvarez, Julia: articles, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Amatulla, Shakurra, 1984; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Amirthanayagam, Indran, 1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Anderson, Kathy, 1993; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Ann Snodgrass, 2002; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 191, Folder 7)
    - Ansa, Tina: correspondence, promotional material, 1995-2002 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Anthony, Michael, 1978; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Arab Poetry Since 9/11, 2002; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 191, Folder 3)
    - Aragon, Margo, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Aragon, Margo: correspondence, 1995-1997 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Aragon, Margo: works by, undated (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Arauz, Susan, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Archer, Chalmers, 1991; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - Asali, Muna, 1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - Ashanti, B.J.: correpondence, works by, 1975-1976 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Ashton, Sallie: correspondence, works by, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Asim, Jabari, 1996-1997; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - Askari, M'Wile Yaw, 1999 September; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 13)
    - Atiba (James Easter), 1975-1976; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 14)
    - Atungaye, Monifa: correspondence, clippings, works, 1990-1993 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Aubert, Alvin, 1980, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 15)
    - Aviles, Quique: biography, correspondence, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Ayala, Naomi: biography and curriculum vitae, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Ayala, Naomi: works by, undated (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Ayala, Naomi: articles and programs, 1995-1996 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Ayala, Naomi: correspondence, 1999-2003 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Babb, Annalee C., 1997; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 16)
    - Babb, Valerie, 1989; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 17)
    - Badini, Munir Ahmed, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 18)
    - Baingana, Doreen: works by, undated (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Baingana, Doreen: correspondence, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Baldwin, Andre J., Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 19)
    - Baldwin, James: articles and profiles, 1985-1998 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Baldwin, James: interviews, 1972-1988 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Baldwin, James: reviews, 1979-1994 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Baldwin, James: works by (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Baldwin, James: obituaries, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Baldwin, James: miscellaneous, 1982-1989 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Bambara, Toni Cade: correspondence, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Bambara, Toni Cade: promotional material, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Bambara, Toni Cade: articles, 1982-1999 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Bambara, Toni Cade: "The Salt Eaters" reviews, 1980b (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Bambara, Toni Cade: works by, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Bambara, Toni Cade: micellaneous, undated (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Bamisaiye, Babatunde O., 1987, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 20)
    - Bandele, Asha: works by, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Banks, Stanley E., 1977-2003; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 72, Folder 21)
    - Baptiste, Mahmoud T., 2006; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Baptiste, Theophilus A., 2007 January; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Baraka, Amiri: correspondence (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Baraka, Amiri: works by, undated (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Baraka, Amiri: reviews, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Baraka, Amiri: interviews, 1974-2003 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Baraka, Amiri: profiles and articles, 1973-2004 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Baraka, Amiri: miscellaneous, undated (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Barbour, Julia: profile, works, clippings, 1972-1980 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Barnet, Juliana, 1998; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Barras, Jonetta: works by [1 of 2], 1984-2005 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Barras, Jonetta: works by [2 of 2], 1984-2005 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Barrett, David, 2002 July 27; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Bartee, Rich, 1974-1977; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Bashira, Damali, 1975-1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 73, Folder 6 (1/3))
    - Bashira, Damali, 1975-1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 73, Folder 7 (2/3))
    - Bashira, Damali, 1975-1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 73, Folder 8 (3/3))
    - Bass, Holly, 1991-2009; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Bayez-Sydner, Bernadine, 1993-1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Bayne, Bijan C., 1994-1997; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Beane, Carol, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Beatty, Ross Jr., 1979; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Beaubien, Michael Charles: works by (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Beaubien, Michael Charles: articles and correspondence, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Becker, Anne, 2007; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Becker, Anne: correspondence, works by, 1988-1994 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Beckham, Rochelle, 1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Bell, Bernard, 1988-1990; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Bell, Eddie, 1996; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - Bellis, Peter Damian, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - Belton, Don, 1995-1996; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - Benedict, Elizabeth: articles, reviews, correspondence, 1988-1993 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Benko, Ralph, 1990; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - Bennett, Renee, 1977, 1981; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 74, Folder 13)
    - Benston, Kimberly, 1983; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 74, Folder 14)
    - Berlet, Chip, 1995-1997; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 124, Folder 1)
    - Berman, Barbara, 2005; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 74, Folder 15)
    - Berman, Barbara: works by, undated (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Berman, Barbara: programs, articles, photographs, miscellaneous, 1982-1987 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Berman, Barbara: correspondence, 1987-1994 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Berman, Barbara: correspondence, 1991-1999 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Berry, Faith: correspondence, clippings, 1984-1986 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Bersee, Thomas, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 74, Folder 16)
    - Berssenbrugge, Mei-Mei, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 74, Folder 17)
    - Betts, Dwayne, 2006-2007; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 74, Folder 18)
    - Bhagat, Ram, 1982-1983; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 74, Folder 19)
    - Bibbs, Hart Leroi, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 74, Folder 20)